<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HRW-Info</string>
    <string name="tab1">Soc</string>
    <string name="tab2">Device</string>
    <string name="tab3">System</string>
    <string name="tab4">Battery</string>
    <string name="tab5">About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main3">MainActivity3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">About</string>
    <string name="battery_health_cold">Cold</string>
    <string name="battery_health_dead">Dead</string>
    <string name="battery_health_good">Good</string>
    <string name="battery_health_over_voltage">Over Voltage</string>
    <string name="battery_health_overheat">Overheat</string>
    <string name="battery_health_unspecified_failure">Unspecified Failure</string>
    <string name="battery_health_unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="battery_plugged_wireless">Wireless</string>
    <string name="battery_plugged_usb">USB</string>
    <string name="battery_plugged_ac">AC Current</string>
    <string name="battery_plugged_none">None</string>
    <string name="battery_status_charging">Charging</string>
    <string name="battery_status_discharging">Discharging</string>
    <string name="battery_status_full">Full</string>
    <string name="battery_status_unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="developed_by">Developed by Domenico Gabriele Aiello</string>
    <string name="contact_me">For any question, contact me at dom.aiello90@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED \"AS IS\", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</string>
    <string name="powered_by">Powered By</string>
    <string name="no_description_popup">No description available</string>
    <string name="arm_general_description">ARM™ (Advanced RISC Machine), is a family of reduced instruction set computing (RISC) architectures for computer processors, developed by the british company ARM Holdings. </string>
    <string name="scaling_governor_generic">The scaling governor parameter indicates the actual power scheme of the CPU. The values of this parameters can be: performance, powersave, userspace, ondemand, conservative or interactive. For further details, see the linux kernel documentation.</string>
    <string name="device_model_description">The device model is used by the manufacturer to uniquely identify its devices.</string>
    <string name="system_uptime_description">The system uptime field indicates how long the device is running.</string>
    <string name="hardware_description">This value should indicate the underlying hardware model of your device. Unfortunately, many manufacturers doesn\'t fill this field correctly or leaves it empty. </string>
    <string name="clusters_description">A cluster array is a combination of different types of processors that works together as a single processing unit. (a single cluster indicates a single processor). Every cluster indicates the number of cores and its max and min frequency values.</string>
    <string name="about_app_name">HRW-Info for Android</string>
    <string name="version_code">Version %s </string>
</resources>
